[{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980273086,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":9390,"timeElapsed":84624},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980280409,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":7321,"timeElapsed":91947},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980295265,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":14853,"timeElapsed":106802},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980310268,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":15002,"timeElapsed":121806},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980322349,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":12079,"timeElapsed":133887},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980330127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":7776,"timeElapsed":141665},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980340676,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":10547,"timeElapsed":152214},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980344491,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3813,"timeElapsed":156029},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980348150,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3658,"timeElapsed":159688},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980368218,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":18149,"timeElapsed":179756},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980383824,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":15605,"timeElapsed":195362},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980389995,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":6169,"timeElapsed":201533},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980394035,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4039,"timeElapsed":205573},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980400549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":6512,"timeElapsed":212087},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980407414,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":6864,"timeElapsed":218952},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980419211,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":11796,"timeElapsed":230749},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980422606,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3394,"timeElapsed":234144},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980430785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":8178,"timeElapsed":242323},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980440555,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":8315,"timeElapsed":252093},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980464325,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":23769,"timeElapsed":275863},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980468538,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":4212,"timeElapsed":280076},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980471056,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2517,"timeElapsed":282594},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980475962,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4905,"timeElapsed":287500},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980480952,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4988,"timeElapsed":292490},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980484656,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":3703,"timeElapsed":296194},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980490972,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6314,"timeElapsed":302510},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980494805,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3831,"timeElapsed":306343},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980498290,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3484,"timeElapsed":309828},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980512541,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":12943,"timeElapsed":324079},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980516908,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4364,"timeElapsed":328445},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980522985,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":6076,"timeElapsed":334523},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980525563,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2577,"timeElapsed":337101},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980530284,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4720,"timeElapsed":341822},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980537286,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":7001,"timeElapsed":348824},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980541235,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3947,"timeElapsed":352773},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980546526,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":5290,"timeElapsed":358064},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980550216,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":3689,"timeElapsed":361754},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980555510,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":5293,"timeElapsed":367048},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980566994,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":9699,"timeElapsed":378532},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980570199,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3204,"timeElapsed":381737},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980574715,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4515,"timeElapsed":386253},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980577207,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2491,"timeElapsed":388745},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980593595,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":16387,"timeElapsed":405133},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980596403,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2806,"timeElapsed":407941},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980601027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":4622,"timeElapsed":412565},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980604854,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3825,"timeElapsed":416392},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980607929,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3074,"timeElapsed":419467},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980615083,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":5538,"timeElapsed":426621},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980617724,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2640,"timeElapsed":429262},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980625735,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":8009,"timeElapsed":437273},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980628107,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2370,"timeElapsed":439645},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980637416,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":9308,"timeElapsed":448954},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980640313,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2895,"timeElapsed":451851},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980644174,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3860,"timeElapsed":455712},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980648280,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4104,"timeElapsed":459818},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980651429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3148,"timeElapsed":462967},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980663592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":10328,"timeElapsed":475130},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980667101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":3508,"timeElapsed":478639},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980672500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":5397,"timeElapsed":484037},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980677181,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":4680,"timeElapsed":488719},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980685431,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":8250,"timeElapsed":496969},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980688095,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":2662,"timeElapsed":499633},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980691866,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3769,"timeElapsed":503404},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980697014,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":5146,"timeElapsed":508552},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980700777,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":3762,"timeElapsed":512315},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980723314,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":20996,"timeElapsed":534851},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980726041,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2725,"timeElapsed":537579},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980731813,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":5771,"timeElapsed":543351},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980735235,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3420,"timeElapsed":546773},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980741850,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":6614,"timeElapsed":553388},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980744153,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":2302,"timeElapsed":555691},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980748313,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4159,"timeElapsed":559851},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980757244,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":8930,"timeElapsed":568782},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980760467,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"238","question":"Did you commute to work today and if so, was there traffic? Was it better or worse than usual?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":3221,"timeElapsed":572005},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980775505,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":13513,"timeElapsed":587043},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980777761,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2255,"timeElapsed":589299},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980793688,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":15925,"timeElapsed":605226},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980796197,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2507,"timeElapsed":607735},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980802555,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":6357,"timeElapsed":614093},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980804825,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2269,"timeElapsed":616363},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980812947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":8120,"timeElapsed":624485},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980818233,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":5284,"timeElapsed":629771},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980821307,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3073,"timeElapsed":632845},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980839329,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":11906,"timeElapsed":650867},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980842333,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3002,"timeElapsed":653870},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980846600,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4266,"timeElapsed":658138},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980857794,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":11193,"timeElapsed":669332},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980863179,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":5384,"timeElapsed":674717},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980871739,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":8557,"timeElapsed":683276},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980875255,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3515,"timeElapsed":686793},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980880583,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":5326,"timeElapsed":692121},{"subjectID":"0y1l4x8eug","prolificID":"5db48b4d14dab8000de45fdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2320fe03360cd2acef2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980884079,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3494,"timeElapsed":695617}]